<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/jekyll-start/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/jekyll-start/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-03-14T21:43:43+02:00</updated><id>/jekyll-start/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Kiwi</title><link href="/jekyll-start/kiwi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kiwi" /><published>2021-03-12T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/jekyll-start/kiwi</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll-start/kiwi/">&lt;p&gt;Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible
berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most common cultivar group of kiwifruit is oval, about the size of a large
hen’s egg (5–8 cm (2.0–3.1 in) in length and 4.5–5.5 cm (1.8–2.2 in) in
diameter). It has a fibrous, dull greenish-brown skin and bright green or
golden flesh with rows of tiny, black, edible seeds. The fruit has a soft
texture, with a sweet and unique flavor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html">Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apples</title><link href="/jekyll-start/apples/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apples" /><published>2021-03-11T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-03-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/jekyll-start/apples</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll-start/apples/">&lt;p&gt;An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple trees are cultivated worldwide, and are the most widely grown species in
the genus Malus. The tree originated in Central Asia, where its wild ancestor,
Malus sieversii, is still found today. Apples have been grown for thousands of
years in Asia and Europe, and were brought to North America by European
colonists.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html">An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wine grapes</title><link href="/jekyll-start/grapes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wine grapes" /><published>2021-03-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-03-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/jekyll-start/grapes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll-start/grapes/">&lt;p&gt;A grape is a fruit, botanically a berry, of the deciduous woody vines of the flowering plant genus Vitis. 
Grapes can be eaten fresh as table grapes or they can be used for making wine, jam, grape juice, 
jelly, grape seed extract, raisins, vinegar, and grape seed oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, 72 million tons of grapes are grown each year worldwide, mostly to produce wine. 
Every year, 7.2 trillion gallons of wine are produced. Grapes are also a popular finger food.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>costa</name></author><summary type="html">A grape is a fruit, botanically a berry, of the deciduous woody vines of the flowering plant genus Vitis. Grapes can be eaten fresh as table grapes or they can be used for making wine, jam, grape juice, jelly, grape seed extract, raisins, vinegar, and grape seed oil.</summary></entry></feed>